# Rohinsha Gajbhiye

**Contact:** +91-9632093522

Address: Hitech City, Hyderabad

**Email:** r2hinsha@gmail.com

Date of Birth: 6<sup>th</sup> April, 1994

Website: rohinsha.github.io



I'm a 24-year-old techie. Graduated as a Computer Engineer from IIIT, Pune and now a pedantic Front-end developer. I am passionate about writing readable code that follows best practices. Innovate, design and code in an extraordinary manner are some key aspects I am good at. Tailoring great user experience. Bringing a designer's concept to life with front-end web technologies and organizing the structure of websites to make them appealing for the users are some of the major tasks. I am currently reviewing pull requests for some cool open source React.js projects.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

#### 1) Equiphunt, Hyderabad - Frontend Developer

November, 2017 - At present

It is one of the portals for B2B marketplace which deals with rental and sale of construction equipments, spare parts and other services related to the equipments. ITSPE is the technology partner of Equiphunt.

- Highway Traffic Management System (HTMS): ITSPE traffic management product, the Traffic Intelligence Server, can be used to manage the Highway Traffic from the control room. HTMS is capable to integrate Variable Message Sign (VMS) boards, Meteorological (MET) sensors, Automatic Traffics Counter & Classifier (ATCC) sensors, CCTV cameras and, Emergency Call Box of any brand and specifications. I had developed and modified all the screens of HTMS for better look and feel.
- Handling the back office modules of equipment.com website, here data will be maintained by Equiphunt team.
- Developed UI and frontend working modules for internal systems which help to cater the needs of suppliers and rentors of equipments.

#### 2) Convergent Technocraft Pvt Ltd, Bangalore - Frontend Developer

July, 2017- Oct, 2017

Interactive, Creative, Scalable, and Measurable Digital marketing solutions. Complete convergence between your different online and offline marketing channels. Connecting business to audience in a unique, innovative, and seamless way. It is a digital asset management company which helps brands achieve their online goals.

- The digital marketing campaign is when your website, blogs, social media channels, offline marketing initiatives are synchronized and optimized to work together seamlessly. To achieve a cohesive digital strategy and presence, my work there was to develop websites and web applications as per client requirements.
- Developed the entire website of Client Beautik Fashions, based out of Bangalore, which offers a full range of unique apparel and accessories to women who value versatility, style, and comfort. We help you choose clothes that represent your personality, mood, ambitions and desires.
- Developed Client's Website Nakshatraveda which is an international organization dedicated towards Vedic Astrology and implementation of Vedic sciences & knowledge to enhance and derive benefits to revive ancient scriptures and literature and promote it for the benefit and upliftment of the human race and to spread positive energy and vibes in people's lives.

#### 3) Infratab, Bangalore - UI Developer Intern

April, 2017 - June, 2017

It is an Internet of things company providing a quality monitoring platform for the perishables\* industries, where their measure freshness and provide customers the tools to make better decisions about their inventory.

- Revamped its official website.
- Created various Dashboard designs for the internal systems which would help their customers in making better decisions in efficiently handling their perishables supply chains to reduce spoilage, protect and improve their brand's identity.

#### **SKILLS**

HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, Jquery, Grunt, Gulp, Materialize CSS, Sass, Bootstrap, React JS.

## **PROJECTS**

#### 1) MouseMove Wheel

Wherever the user will click in the viewport with the mouse, the mouse-move event will be fired in which 4 different arbitrary co-ordinate positions will get the same center text duplicated in them. Only the font color will change for every co-ordinate position.

#### 2) Gold Gym Website

It is a minimal promotional based responsive website of gym with different menu options in it, such as diets and nutrition, more details about workouts and exercises.

#### 3) Random Quote Generator

It has fetched quotes which gets displayed when the user clicks on the button.

#### 4) Box8-online food ordering and delivery website cloning

Clone of the home page of Box8 has been cloned in a similar fashion.

#### 5) Speech Synthesis

A voice over bot speaks the text that the user inputs in the input field. Supports customization of different combinations of speech and rate.

#### 6) Coming Soon Template

Simple, responsive and appealing user experience coming soon page.

#### 7) Graphical Password Authentication for Cloud Security

Platform: Java

Technology: Cloud Computing

**Description**: This project provides a secure system for the storage and access of cloud services Users can easily login into the system as it provides 3 level authentication scheme with textual, graphical and one time passwords with an option of uploading and downloading any type of files on the cloud which uses Centered Discretization and Persuasive cued click points. (PCCP).

### 8) Title: Bluetooth Chat Application

Platform: Android and Java

**Description:** It was a mini-project that deals as a messenger for android based phones. Via Bluetooth as the communication medium within a specified range, users can send messages to each other without the use of any Wi-Fi or internet access.

# **EDUCATION**

Examination	Board/University	School /College	Percentage	Year
10 <sup>th</sup>	SSC (Maharashtra)	J.N Tata Parsi Girl's High School, Nagpur	83	2009
12 <sup>th</sup>	HSC (Maharashtra)	Sindhu Mahavidyalaya, Nagpur	73	2011
B.E (Computer Science)	Pune University	International Institute of Information Technology, Pune	61.4	2015

# Rohinsha Gajbhiye

**Contact:** +91-9632093522

Address: Hitech City, Hyderabad

**Email:** r2hinsha@gmail.com

Date of Birth: 6<sup>th</sup> April, 1994

Website: rohinsha.github.io



I'm a 24-year-old techie. Graduated as a Computer Engineer from IIIT, Pune and now a pedantic Front-end developer. I am passionate about writing readable code that follows best practices. Innovate, design and code in an extraordinary manner are some key aspects I am good at. Tailoring great user experience. Bringing a designer's concept to life with front-end web technologies and organizing the structure of websites to make them appealing for the users are some of the major tasks. I am currently reviewing pull requests for some cool open source React.js projects.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

#### 1) Equiphunt, Hyderabad - Frontend Developer

November, 2017 - At present

It is one of the portals for B2B marketplace which deals with rental and sale of construction equipments, spare parts and other services related to the equipments. ITSPE is the technology partner of Equiphunt.

- Highway Traffic Management System (HTMS): ITSPE traffic management product, the Traffic Intelligence Server, can be used to manage the Highway Traffic from the control room. HTMS is capable to integrate Variable Message Sign (VMS) boards, Meteorological (MET) sensors, Automatic Traffics Counter & Classifier (ATCC) sensors, CCTV cameras and, Emergency Call Box of any brand and specifications. I had developed and modified all the screens of HTMS for better look and feel.
- Handling the back office modules of equipment.com website, here data will be maintained by Equiphunt team.
- Developed UI and frontend working modules for internal systems which help to cater the needs of suppliers and rentors of equipments.

#### 2) Convergent Technocraft Pvt Ltd, Bangalore - Frontend Developer

July, 2017- Oct, 2017

Interactive, Creative, Scalable, and Measurable Digital marketing solutions. Complete convergence between your different online and offline marketing channels. Connecting business to audience in a unique, innovative, and seamless way. It is a digital asset management company which helps brands achieve their online goals.

- The digital marketing campaign is when your website, blogs, social media channels, offline marketing initiatives are synchronized and optimized to work together seamlessly. To achieve a cohesive digital strategy and presence, my work there was to develop websites and web applications as per client requirements.
- Developed the entire website of Client Beautik Fashions, based out of Bangalore, which offers a full range of unique apparel and accessories to women who value versatility, style, and comfort. We help you choose clothes that represent your personality, mood, ambitions and desires.
- Developed Client's Website Nakshatraveda which is an international organization dedicated towards Vedic Astrology and implementation of Vedic sciences & knowledge to enhance and derive benefits to revive ancient scriptures and literature and promote it for the benefit and upliftment of the human race and to spread positive energy and vibes in people's lives.

#### 3) Infratab, Bangalore - UI Developer Intern

April, 2017 - June, 2017

It is an Internet of things company providing a quality monitoring platform for the perishables\* industries, where their measure freshness and provide customers the tools to make better decisions about their inventory.

- Revamped its official website.
- Created various Dashboard designs for the internal systems which would help their customers in making better decisions in efficiently handling their perishables supply chains to reduce spoilage, protect and improve their brand's identity.

#### **SKILLS**

HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, Jquery, Grunt, Gulp, Materialize CSS, Sass, Bootstrap, React JS.

## **PROJECTS**

#### 1) MouseMove Wheel

Wherever the user will click in the viewport with the mouse, the mouse-move event will be fired in which 4 different arbitrary co-ordinate positions will get the same center text duplicated in them. Only the font color will change for every co-ordinate position.

#### 2) Gold Gym Website

It is a minimal promotional based responsive website of gym with different menu options in it, such as diets and nutrition, more details about workouts and exercises.

#### 3) Random Quote Generator

It has fetched quotes which gets displayed when the user clicks on the button.

#### 4) Box8-online food ordering and delivery website cloning

Clone of the home page of Box8 has been cloned in a similar fashion.

#### 5) Speech Synthesis

A voice over bot speaks the text that the user inputs in the input field. Supports customization of different combinations of speech and rate.

#### 6) Coming Soon Template

Simple, responsive and appealing user experience coming soon page.

#### 7) Graphical Password Authentication for Cloud Security

Platform: Java

Technology: Cloud Computing

**Description**: This project provides a secure system for the storage and access of cloud services Users can easily login into the system as it provides 3 level authentication scheme with textual, graphical and one time passwords with an option of uploading and downloading any type of files on the cloud which uses Centered Discretization and Persuasive cued click points. (PCCP).

### 8) Title: Bluetooth Chat Application

Platform: Android and Java

**Description:** It was a mini-project that deals as a messenger for android based phones. Via Bluetooth as the communication medium within a specified range, users can send messages to each other without the use of any Wi-Fi or internet access.

# **EDUCATION**

Examination	Board/University	School /College	Percentage	Year
10 <sup>th</sup>	SSC (Maharashtra)	J.N Tata Parsi Girl's High School, Nagpur	83	2009
12 <sup>th</sup>	HSC (Maharashtra)	Sindhu Mahavidyalaya, Nagpur	73	2011
B.E (Computer Science)	Pune University	International Institute of Information Technology, Pune	61.4	2015